Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Cinerama premiere (Detroit, Michigan), 1953 February - March; 7 (Box 1540)
    - Note: DETROIT PREMIERE - Crack precision drill squadron from University of Detroit Air Reserves perform front of Music hall at Midwest premiere, Tuesday, Fe. 11 (Note: first time that snowflakes have ever taken this form in my newspaper career, usually streaks are the effect); From: Bill Green, Cinerama, 2
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama executives Lowell Thomas (right) and Joseph Kaufman inspect one of the Welcome discs which decorated many streetlight posts in downtown Detroit, 3
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama executives Lowell Thomas (right) and Joseph Kaufman inspect one of the Welcome discs which decorated many streetlight posts in downtown Detroit, 3-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama executives Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left) president; and Lowell Thomas, vice-chairman of the board, 4
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama executives Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left) president; and Lowell Thomas, vice-chairman of the board, 4-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left) president of Cinerama Productions Corp., with Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the board, and Kathy Darlyn, pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This Is Cinerama", 5
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left) president of Cinerama Productions Corp., with Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the board, and Kathy Darlyn, pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This Is Cinerama", 5-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Lowell Thomas (right) vice-chairman of the Cinerama board, discusses premiere plans with Joseph Kaufman (left), director of exhibition, and Kathy Darlyn (center), pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This is Cinerama", 6
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Lowell Thomas (right) vice-chairman of the Cinerama board, discusses premiere plans with Joseph Kaufman (left), director of exhibition, and Kathy Darlyn (center), pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This is Cinerama", 6-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama's director of exhibition Joseph Kaufman (left) welcomes to Detroit Lowell Thomas, vice-chairman of the board, and Kathy Darlyn, pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This is Cinerama", 7
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama's director of exhibition Joseph Kaufman (left) welcomes to Detroit Lowell Thomas, vice-chairman of the board, and Kathy Darlyn, pretty water-ski champion appearing in "This is Cinerama", 7-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama's director of exhibition Joseph Kaufman (left) and Mrs. Kaufman (second from left) with their premiere guests Mr. and Mrs. Edward Slotkin, 8
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama's director of exhibition Joseph Kaufman (left) and Mrs. Kaufman (second from left) with their premiere guests Mr. and Mrs. Edward Slotkin, 8-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left), president of Cinerama, and Joseph Kaufman, director of exhibition, inspect the theater's signs, 9
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Dudley Roberts, Jr. (left), president of Cinerama, and Joseph Kaufman, director of exhibition, inspect the theater's signs, 9-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Walter Thompson (second from left) who supervised the prologue of "This is Cinerama", and his premiere guests - Vera Peterson (left) of Los Angeles; Mrs. Mary E. Vanstone; and Rolin Stonebrook, manager of the Palace Theater in Chicago, 10
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Walter Thompson (second from left) who supervised the prologue of "This is Cinerama", and his premiere guests - Vera Peterson (left) of Los Angeles; Mrs. Mary E. Vanstone; and Rolin Stonebrook, manager of the Palace Theater in Chicago, 10-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Joseph Kaufman (left), Cinerama's director of exhibition, with Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 11
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Joseph Kaufman (left), Cinerama's director of exhibition, with Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 11-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Lowell Thomas (left), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board, with Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 12
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Lowell Thomas (left), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board, with Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 12-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 13
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 13-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 14
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Michigan's Governor G. Mennen Williams and Mrs. Williams, 14-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Mrs. Graham A. Sellers (left) and Mrs. Harold L. Frank of the Women's Association for the Detroit Symphony Orchestra - under whose sponsorship the premiere was held - are given the Cinerama Week proclamation by Mayor Albert E. Cobo, 15
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Mrs. Graham A. Sellers (left) and Mrs. Harold L. Frank of the Women's Association for the Detroit Symphony Orchestra - under whose sponsorship the premiere was held - are given the Cinerama Week proclamation by Mayor Albert E. Cobo, 15-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; K. T. Keller, famed Chrysler executive (second from right) and his party arrive for the premiere, 16
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; K. T. Keller, famed Chrysler executive (second from right) and his party arrive for the premiere, 16-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Vernon C. Myers (left), publisher of Look Magazine, presents his publication's Special Cinerama Award to Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board. Dick Osgood (center) "Show World" commentator of radio station WXYZ, broadcasts the presentation from the lobby, 17
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Vernon C. Myers (left), publisher of Look Magazine, presents his publication's Special Cinerama Award to Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board. Dick Osgood (center) "Show World" commentator of radio station WXYZ, broadcasts the presentation from the lobby, 17-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Vernon C. Myers (left), publisher of Look Magazine, presents his publication's Special Cinerama Award to Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board. Dick Osgood (center) "Show World" commentator of radio station WXYZ, broadcasts the presentation from the lobby, 18
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Vernon C. Myers (left), publisher of Look Magazine, presents his publication's Special Cinerama Award to Lowell Thomas (right), vice-chairman of the Cinerama board. Dick Osgood (center) "Show World" commentator of radio station WXYZ, broadcasts the presentation from the lobby, 18-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama;s red carpet in front of the theater. Lettering is in gold, 19
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; Cinerama;s red carpet in front of the theater. Lettering is in gold, 19-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; One of the welcome discs which decorated streetlight posts on many of the streets in downtown Detroit, 20
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; One of the welcome discs which decorated streetlight posts on many of the streets in downtown Detroit, 20-verso
    - CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; The refreshment bar in the lounge, 21
    - Verso: CINERAMA PREMIERE - DETROIT, MICHIGAN - MUSIC HALL - MARCH 23, 1953; The refreshment bar in the lounge, 21-verso
    - [Cinerama Music Hall], 22
    - [Cinerama Music Hall], 23
    - [Cinerama Music Hall], 24
    - [Cinerama Music Hall], 25
  - Subject files: Cinerama premiere (Washington, D.C.), 1953 November 5; 8 (Box 1540)
    - FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; Monsieur Seyeoux, Minister of the French Embassy, expressing delight to Lowell Thomas at seeing "Cinerama", 1
    - Verso: FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; Monsieur Seyeoux, Minister of the French Embassy, expressing delight to Lowell Thomas at seeing "Cinerama", 1-verso
    - FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; The Honorable and Mrs. Joseph C. Grew, former Ambassador to Japan, chatting with Hazard Reeves and Lowell Thomas during Intermission, 2
    - Verso: FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; The Honorable and Mrs. Joseph C. Grew, former Ambassador to Japan, chatting with Hazard Reeves and Lowell Thomas during Intermission, 2-verso
    - FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; Mr. Fred Waller, inventor of Cinerama, and Lowell Thomas, Vice President and narrator of "This Is Cinerama", arriving at Premiere, 3
    - Verso: FROM - John Joseph; Washington, D.C. Premiere, "This is Cinerama", Warner Theatre, Thursday night - 11/5/1953; Mr. Fred Waller, inventor of Cinerama, and Lowell Thomas, Vice President and narrator of "This Is Cinerama", arriving at Premiere, 3-verso
  - Subject files: Cinerama (President Dwight Eisenhower and Lowell Thomas), 1955; 9 (Box 1540)
    - [President Dwight Eisenhower and Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Subject files: Cinerama (Seven Wonders of the World), circa 1956; 10 (Box 1540)
    - Lowell Thomas, producer of the third Cinerama adventure, "Seven Wonders of the World," examines a model of the Sphinx with pretty Eileen Salama. Miss Salama handled all the advance arrangements for the Cinerama expedition during its visit to one of the most remote corners of the world, Wadi Beihan in southern Arabia. There Cinerama camera men filmed a stampede of thousands of camels and were guests of honor at a banquet held by the fabulous Sherif Hussein, 1
    - Note: Lowell Thomas, producer of the third Cinerama adventure, "Seven Wonders of the World," examines a model of the Sphinx with pretty Eileen Salama. Miss Salama handled all the advance arrangements for the Cinerama expedition during its visit to one of the most remote corners of the world, Wadi Beihan in southern Arabia. There Cinerama camera men filmed a stampede of thousands of camels and were guests of honor at a banquet held by the fabulous Sherif Hussein, 2
    - The beautiful Taj Mahal, one of the wonders of the modern world, with Lalitha Bhatt. The model, valued at over $3,000 and owned by J. J. Singh of the India Shop in New York City, is made entirely of marble like the original, 3
    - Note: Lowell Thomas, producer of the newest Cinerama picture, "Seven Wonders of the World," examines a model of the beautiful Taj Mahal, one of the wonders of the modern world, with Lalitha Bhatt. The model, valued at over $3,000 and owned by J. J. Singh of the India Shop in New York City, is made entirely of marble like the original, 4
    - East and West meet over a Japanese pagoda as Morigai Mitsuko instructs Lowell Thomas in the finer points of Oriental architecture. The noted commentator, producer of the new Cinerama adventure, "Seven Wonders of the World," spent several months of intensive research before starting to shoot sequences in Japan, 5
    - Note: East and West meet over a Japanese pagoda as Morigai Mitsuko instructs Lowell Thomas in the finer points of Oriental architecture. The noted commentator, producer of the new Cinerama adventure, "Seven Wonders of the World," spent several months of intensive research before starting to shoot sequences in Japan, 6
    - Fascinating Lake Baikal, in Central Siberia. It is the deepest in the world (almost a mile deep) and 353 miles long. 1800 species of plant and animal life have been identified; ¾ of them are found no place else on earth. It is a highlight of both the 8-day and 15-day Alaska Airlines tour. Intourist photograph, 7
    - Verso: Fascinating Lake Baikal, in Central Siberia. It is the deepest in the world (almost a mile deep) and 353 miles long. 1800 species of plant and animal life have been identified; ¾ of them are found no place else on earth. It is a highlight of both the 8-day and 15-day Alaska Airlines tour. Intourist photograph, 7-verso
    - Photograph from Intourist; Samarkand in Russia's Central Asia is a delightful mixture of the surrounding countries, truly the land of the Arabian Nights. Crossroads of historic camel caravans and ravaging warlords. The ruins of Tamerlane's early 15th century Tomb, and other turquoise-colored tile domes ar a photographer's delight, 8
    - Verso: Photograph from Intourist; Samarkand in Russia's Central Asia is a delightful mixture of the surrounding countries, truly the land of the Arabian Nights. Crossroads of historic camel caravans and ravaging warlords. The ruins of Tamerlane's early 15th century Tomb, and other turquoise-colored tile domes ar a photographer's delight, 8-verso
    - Moscow River and The Kremlin, which is an historic, walled fortress in the center of Moscow. Many of its most famous buildings are now museums. A complete tour is included in Alaska Airlines 15-day, all-inclusive tours out of Anchorage. Moscow River in foreground; Intourist photo, 9
    - Verso: Moscow River and The Kremlin, which is an historic, walled fortress in the center of Moscow. Many of its most famous buildings are now museums. A complete tour is included in Alaska Airlines 15-day, all-inclusive tours out of Anchorage. Moscow River in foreground; Intourist photo, 9-verso
  - Subject files: Cinerama (Aut Swenson Thrillcade), circa 1950s; 11 (Box 1540)
    - Caption: Headed your way, the Aut Swenson Thrillcade, jumbo of all thrill shows, 1
    - Caption: A '56 Ford Sunliner in a ramp-to-ramp leap over dancing Dyna ', 2 ton pachyderm, at the Provincial Exhibition of Manitoba and Western Canada Trade Fair, Brandon, Manitoba July 5th. An alert photographer of the Winnipeg Free Press snapped this prize-winning photo which appeared on the front page of the Winnipeg Free Press, July 6th edition; This same stunt will be repeated at the State Fair of Oklahoma at Oklahoma City, September 24-29 when the Aut Swenson Thrillcade combined with star-studded hippodrome features will be presented before afternoon grandstand throngs, 2
  - Subject files: Cinerama (United States Camera Achievement Award), circa 1952; 12 (Box 1540)
    - U.S. Camera Achievement Award Luncheon, 1
    - Verso: U.S. Camera Achievement Award Luncheon, 1-verso
    - U.S. Camera Achievement Award Luncheon, 2
    - U.S. Camera Achievement Award Luncheon, 3
  - Subject files: Cinerama (The Wonders of Cinerama photographic exhibition), circa 1950s; 13 (Box 1540)
    - [Women walking around The Wonders of Cinerama photographic exhibition], 1
    - [Guests looking at photos at The Wonders of Cinerama photographic exhibition], 2
    - [The Cinerama Photographic Expedition gallery], 3
    - [Man putting up photographs for The Wonders of Cinerama photographic exhibition], 4
    - Edwin Sippel, Pan American co-pilot and navigator for Lowell Thomas's "Seven Wonders of the World" movie-making expedition, is an ardent amateur photographer whose first exhibit "The Wonders of Cinerama" is now on view at the (exhibition hall) in (city). This exhibition is the result of a year-long journey to the remotest corners of the earth, 5
    - Note: Edwin Sippel, Pan American co-pilot and navigator for Lowell Thomas's "Seven Wonders of the World" movie-making expedition, is an ardent amateur photographer whose first exhibit "The Wonders of Cinerama" is now on view at the (exhibition hall) in (city). This exhibition is the result of a year-long journey to the remotest corners of the earth, 6
    - Cinerama co-pilot Ed Sippel stands on a dock along the Victoria Nile River photographing some of the marvels of Egypt that can be seen in his first photographic exhibition, "The Wonders of Cinerama," now showing at the (exhibition hall) in (city). Sippel was navigator for Lowell Thomas's trip around the world when the noted commentator was filming "Seven Wonders of the World," the Cinerama adventure now playing at the (theatre) in (city), 7
    - Note: Cinerama co-pilot Ed Sippel stands on a dock along the Victoria Nile River photographing some of the marvels of Egypt that can be seen in his first photographic exhibition, "The Wonders of Cinerama," now showing at the (exhibition hall) in (city). Sippel was navigator for Lowell Thomas's trip around the world when the noted commentator was filming "Seven Wonders of the World," the Cinerama adventure now playing at the (theatre) in (city), 8
    - Harry Squire (on the right), Director of Photography for Lowell Thomas's Cinerama production, "Seven Wonders of the World," now playing at the (theatre) in (city), and nominee for an Academy Award last year, chats with his protege, Ed Sippel, in Mysore City, India. A Pan American co-pilot and amateur photographer, Sippel has his first picture exhibit, "The Wonders of Cinerama," on view at the (exhibition hall) in (city), 9
    - Note: Harry Squire (on the right), Director of Photography for Lowell Thomas's Cinerama production, "Seven Wonders of the World," now playing at the (theatre) in (city), and nominee for an Academy Award last year, chats with his protege, Ed Sippel, in Mysore City, India. A Pan American co-pilot and amateur photographer, Sippel has his first picture exhibit, "The Wonders of Cinerama," on view at the (exhibition hall) in (city), 10
    - One of the features of "Wonders of Cinerama," the new photographic exhibit at the (exhibition hall) in (city), is a pictorial essay on the ancient art of Yoga. This Yogi comes from Benares, India where scenes were filmed for Lowell Thomas' latest Cinerama production, "Seven Wonders of the World," now on view at the (theatre) in (city), 11
    - Note: One of the features of "Wonders of Cinerama," the new photographic exhibit at the (exhibition hall) in (city), is a pictorial essay on the ancient art of Yoga. This Yogi comes from Benares, India where scenes were filmed for Lowell Thomas' latest Cinerama production, "Seven Wonders of the World," now on view at the (theatre) in (city), 12
    - This Bedouin warrior is a member of the nomadic tribe of Sherif Hussein, chieftain of Southern Arabia who is one of the photographic highlights of the new "Wonders of Cinerama" photo exhibit now showing at the (exhibition hall) in (city). In his trip around the globe filming "Seven Wonders of the World," now on view at the (theatre), Lowell Thomas visited his old friend, the Sherif, whom he first met when tracking down the story of Lawrence of Arabia, 13
    - Note: This Bedouin warrior is a member of the nomadic tribe of Sherif Hussein, chieftain of Southern Arabia who is one of the photographic highlights of the new "Wonders of Cinerama" photo exhibit now showing at the (exhibition hall) in (city). In his trip around the globe filming "Seven Wonders of the World," now on view at the (theatre), Lowell Thomas visited his old friend, the Sherif, whom he first met when tracking down the story of Lawrence of Arabia, 14
  - Subject files: Dutch Clark, circa 1930s; 14 (Box 1540)
    - Caption: [signed]To Lowell Thomas Jr., from Dutch Clark, 1
  - Subject files: Clover Brook, 1935; 15 (Box 1540)
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed 1935, 1
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed 1935, 1-verso
    - The kitchen door and the staff. Notice the bell on the roof of the porch. Jesse and Mae are on the left. Tom is Mrs. Wise's cook and has been with her 27 years, 2
    - Verso: The kitchen door and the staff. Notice the bell on the roof of the porch. Jesse and Mae are on the left. Tom is Mrs. Wise's cook and has been with her 27 years, 2-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 3
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 3-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 4
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 4-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 5
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 5-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 6
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 6-verso
    - Mrs. Wise's grand-daughter, Barbara, and the south east corner of the house, 7
    - Verso: Mrs. Wise's grand-daughter, Barbara, and the south east corner of the house, 7-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted June1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 8
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted June1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 8-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 9
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted April 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 9-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 10
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 10-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 11
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, Pawling N.Y., Planted May 1935, Photographed Aug. 1935, 11-verso
    - [The home of Lowell Thomas in Pawling, New York], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas in a horse drawn sleigh outside of his house in Pawling, New York], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas's house in Pawling, New York], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas's house in Pawling, New York], 15
  - Subject files: Clover Brook, undated; 16 (Box 1540)
    - [Furnished girl's bedroom in Clover Brook], 1
    - [Living room in Clover Brook], 2
    - [Small seating area in Clover Brook], 3
    - [Library with a portrait of Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) in Clover Brook], 4
    - [Nicely furnished bedroom in Clover Brook], 5